[Music]
[Laughter]
Oh,
tribal sir,
tribalism is our homeland, that's why everyone
gathers like that. There are
thousands of changes in their lives.
This is a beautiful time on earth. Let's all
escape. Come back here.
What's that injury?
The tiger is jealous, sir.
Tiger?
Oh, my friend, Puliveshi, I'm so happy that my hand is
bleeding.  Nail-biting
poison arrow.
Hey, better understand your language and try
to control your cell. Understand
Anaconda.
Watch Titanic. Watch Jurassic Park. Watch a boat next door. Go to the wine
shop next door. Don't go to Bad Boys. You're being told to escape and go home. Don't go far. Don't get caught. Police car.
Police car.  Everything is watching,
policeman, take your hand off the shirt
.  This is the big Manmadharasa, the
policeman.
What kind of a simple man is the policeman in Tamil Nadu today?
Police car, raise your hand, police car,
police car.   I'll
tell you to let your leader know that you're like a damaged tank truck.
What did you hear?
Where is your leader?   Don't
talk about him, policeman.   Why not
?
Do you know what he did?
What did he do?
Turn around like this
[screaming] Run
Judy Joe,
look at me
[music] Hey Judy Joe, look at me
Hey, what's up with the rice?
Call all these people and come to my room and
tell your sister-in-law, I'll
bite you.  This person is
not doing all this insulting work.  These are
all my friends.
What is this quarter ticket or half ticket,
your friend?  [Laughter]
Go outside.
Hey, even if I go outside,
I have equal rights in this room.  Dad
told me.
What is that, a full moon, that's right?
[Laughter]
Now go and see.
Sachin Tendulkar
has come to this neighboring street.  I don't
even have a good shirt to buy an autograph from him
.  Push it all away and it will all fall apart
.  This is another toy,
brother, really Sachin,
yes Sachin has come, and his sister
Aishwarya Rai has come, they were shooting an ad film on the next street, and they
both
disappeared like lightning.
Where is he? Where is he? Who is he? This economy is
Japan's economy. This economy is Japan's economy. This economy is the best economy. This economy is the
best economy. This economy is Indian
economy.
Police Academy Part One Part 2. Did we
fight on the street and
come here to study like a good boy
?  Raska
Akka Nammi is a police officer, Mommy.
This is not a police station, this is our home.
Since 6:00 in the morning, he has been sitting in his room,
studying sincerely
.  He went [laughter]
Indian economy is always his economy. The
first boy in this world who studies in a skirt will be your boy
.   I
thought to myself, "Let's tie my skirt." I did
n't recognize him in my eagerness to study. I
lied and didn't believe anything he said. He just
jumped in from upstairs a while ago
.  You've come like a curry to my train engine
.   Is it
all his work?
Do you know that he left us stranded on the streets, saying that Sachin and Aishwarya Rai were shooting?
I didn't say that, but
Sachidananda Swamiji has
come to the temple next door.  I told him that if he went and
received blessings, he would find wealth
.
What if you, realizing that it was Sachin, took an autorickshaw and went looking for Aishwarya?
As Vadivel says,
there is a small treasure.  Look, Dad.
Hey, I'm just
waiting for you to write all four Aryan papers and pass.
That won't happen, you're just studying.
He's just saying, "Kabadi, Kabadi."
Dad, I forgot all that a long time ago. If you don't
believe me, ask
your mother.
Yes, no,
my dear. I'm the one who
talks a lot.  Did you go to Seppiya's house and
play?
Your father is not around,
why am I telling you this? It's just food,
man. Your father also buys you
every dinosaur shape for revenge,
uncle [laughter]. You're
not going to be a sokka today.
Your father's party is confusing
everyone
.   I'll tell you what kind of
great power Vijayakantha has in his heart. I'll tell you what I
think,
but your father is a very good policeman
.   We have been
following you for 24 hours
.  How are you coping with that?   Did
that guy do divers without speaking?
Oh my god,
aunty, I've been having a hard time for a long time.
You answer the question I ask respectfully.  Does your father
only put kanji on the dress, or does he
take out the four lots?  Why does he
look so different?   He's going to be gone for
a day.   "
Brother,
have you forgotten what I was going to tell you?" Kada
Kumara gets another jolt and extends it.
Then the
police intervened in our mother's liquor case, my dear
.   Don't
worry about him.  I'm not the only one who has a
terrible culture in the match.  Well, it's up to
you to decide tomorrow's match
.
He will have a terrible time helping us,
Dad, is he a wrong number, wrong
number, wrong friends, my
son is a Tendulkar in cricket,
a joy in chess, I can proudly say.
It seems that Poruki and Pasanga are also playing kabaddi together.  Did
you read the names of your friends?
What is the name of the Discovery Channel you were talking about?  What the
hell, I'm so tired of being cut off.   There's nothing
else, Aunty, tomorrow morning at 11 am,
you're going to have a great time at the Ambedkar match
.  Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi Kabaddi
Mama, you brought your phone to your dad
.   Hey,
Arnold, give up the title
.
I'm your father speaking.
I am your father.  Oh, please put Telugu in the
title.
I will kill you if I can get my hands on you, Raska.
Which fox?
Sad fox.
Why sir, tomorrow morning at 11 am at
Ambedkar Ground, Kabaddi Hey
Race Snake Alara
Chop Stop, what lip is moving?
One or the other, one or the other, this is
Madam's concentration work, this is
Oma Kamnu Ukaranum.   Listen
to what Sami says, you have to
study well, right? Okay, okay,
concentration. This is it. Let's
[shouting] start.
The match is going on in a very tough manner. Who is going to
win? The Killi team or the
Tiger team? Next right? [
shouting] Kabadi   There will
be no
[laughter] Look,
what's there? Take some ghee and buy it.
What are you doing here? Sit down, sit down, sit down.
Your
son will go.
[shouting] Take some ghee, come, take   Should
I go? Is that the
end of it? What do you say?   I
say no.
I don't need to respect anyone who doesn't respect my family
.
No, you don't respect it.  What are you doing
?
You go.  My mother has an important
job, so I won't go. If
no one from our house goes to that wedding, they'll think it's their fault. It's too
loud. Velu went and got an
attendant. Do
n't worry,
what kind of parliament is this? It's like
shouting like this. It's just a matter of writing four papers
.  Let the children
study without any worries.
Velu, tell me yourself, did anyone from my parents'
family come to their 60th wedding
?
Why didn't you come, Dad, you came late to me
.   Is it
his brother's daughter's wedding now?
Should I go to Trichy for that?
I wonder how that is possible?  Did
she tell anyone not to step on the door of the house?
Hey, what are you doing, are you supporting your mother or
not? I'm just saying that
I know how much my mother's grandfather and grandmother must have hurt her mentally. I'll remember that
incident right before my eyes. As
for me, not
even a single person from this house should go to that wedding.
Okay, okay, whatever it is, just speak quietly.
I have to study.
You go and study, don't you?   He doesn't know
what my book is, so he bought it for me, and now
he doesn't know what Poovi's book is.
If you know, just go and
study, sir.
Brother,
brother, we have been selected for the semi-finals
.   We will
go to Madurai on the 18th
to play a match.  Sir, I'm going to
tell you to go and play a
match in Madurai on the 18th. Hey,
how many
times have I told you that I have an important conference on the 18th?
What should I do?
Dad, I went and
thought about it 12 times for a minute and it seemed to me that what you
said was correct.
Someone from our house has to go to the wedding in Trichy on the 18th.   I'm
telling you the truth, I suddenly don't have the support to support my father.
I
told him then that he had told me not to step on the door of the house without permission.  But now, what is Thiruvalluvar saying? He has
said that if he did this, he would have done something good for himself.  If you do as this person says, the whole
world will suffer.
Okay, Velu, I'll go and come back myself.
How can you go? They insulted you.
Yes or no, yes or no.
Just
say something.
Yes, only.
However, someone has to leave our house
.  If they send a child to Buwanawa, they
can't tell who is sending them for what.  It's
impossible.
I didn't say anything, I just
said it now,
I said I didn't say anything,
that's what I said, you
idiot,
what are you doing going to the wedding yourself?
17 There 16 Here 18 It's impossible Not possible
At all That's all for
nothing Send him alone
Hey you go
What are you talking about You're stuck I'll go and
join you.
Mix it up, kabaddi kabaddi kabaddi kabaddi
[laughter]
Velu Jacket
Hey, what a little kid he is,
doesn't he know?
Time is running out, I'm
going to a wedding, why bother with books?
It's a six-hour journey to Trichy. Why waste that
time? I'll just take them with me and
study for the Ariya exam right away.   Is all
this too much?  I ca
n't.  Is there no one here to listen to him?   Please do me a
favor and adopt someone
.  Otherwise, take them to the nursing
home.   Is
that a nursing home for the elderly, Father
?  Children's shelter.   I've always been
suspicious of Andy whenever I see him.  Then
Velu and your father
will be very close, even if they are just friends.  They said they would be
a little more generous.
Why does my father always
talk badly about his relatives?
They are all very good people.
No,
she has no other job.
Put it on, put it on.  You are responsible for the expenses.
Spend ₹100 or so.  If you
see this cat drinking,
you'll be drinking the same cat.  Is this why there's so much
build-up?
What?
Okay, okay, I'll come.
Hey,
what is it?   Do
n't forget this and fight.
What is this?
Gift silver jug.  Your father
searched hard for it and bought it.
Price 8000 rupees.
You can do it by stabbing it.  Don't be afraid to make a pot,
bring a pot, a pot of water, a pot of water, a pot of water,
what is
this? Write only your father's name on the note,
or write your name as well. Write
a lot of names,
write a lot of names. There is no
rain in the country, there is no agriculture. The
poor are suffering without water, but
how come only your gang keeps getting water?
As long as you are in trouble, we have
money in our hands. If we all become
lazy,
we will go to Rajasthan.
Can we start the concert soon?
Hey, indigenous people, oppressed people.   Please,
Velu
.  Hit it well.  I didn't
go to the wedding, but you're determined to eat and lick it.
Beat me until you're done. It's as if I've heard everything you've said. They say that only a child can understand a father's mind. Why don't you stop talking? It's not time to play. Dad, the reason I didn't go to the wedding is because you're asking me how this biscuit is in this place. How did you catch it? I was on the train,
studying.
Someone from the opposite side came up to me and started
talking.  I also
talked to him.  In return, he
gave me this biscuit.
You
buy biscuits from Kandavan and eat them no matter what.
He was as decent as his father, I guess
.
Okay, okay, so what happened?   I
only remember eating one biscuit from this.  I was
standing alone at Tirunelveli station, blinded by the light.   I
can't believe I was standing at Tirunelveli station.
Okay, I was just kidding.  That's what's
important now.  Emma, ​​I always ask, "
Is there a pigeon?"
Tell me if she's like that.
Where did you leave it?
Where is that silver shop at Tirunelveli station?
Why are you going to school at this time of day?   There is no
school, there is no silverware.
Silver Hall, yes, silver hall,
you are welcome.  That silver is the
silversmith.  Oh, what's the point of
that now?
Dad, I'm thinking.  [Laughter]
I'm thinking.  You
need to think more about it than just saying what happened.  He came to this mess and
mixed it with that biscuit, and
he hit that silver jug ​​to make it work.   Did
you file a complaint with the railway police?
This is a good question.
Hey, answer me.
A police officer is a boy.
What a
shame it would be for my father if I went and complained about plagiarism.  Oh, Dad, I still ca
n't believe it.  There's only one way to make them believe
.  Was everything I said true then?   Is it
true, Bhuvana?
Oh, no, no, no, no
.  I swore
to my grandmother that I would come to the State First.
Oh my god, grandma and grandpa, can't we just
swear by the truth?
Oh
my God,
what is this, Papa? My
mother is my beloved.
Complain to your father and he will find it and give it to you
.
No, you took it.
Hey hey hey.
What's up, Mom?  This guy stole my money
.  It's okay for a policeman to steal
.  Andy preaches too much, he also
gets into fights, so whenever
you see him, you're welcome, you're welcome, you're welcome
[music]
Okay, okay, I'll call you later.
Where is Puri from here?
Very sad, I can't make you a Puri yet
.
Hey, I saw it.
You've been used to wearing khaki for 24 hours, and no matter what you look at, it looks like a khaki-colored Puri.  It
was like a fire.
Oh my, you're not the one who
said, "Look at her, look at her," and then ate 12
pooris and sat there like a bulldozer
.
Bring the puri,
oh father, all the puri is gone.
Mom, please give me that old sot, I'm so
hungry.
You're welcome,
my mother's preparation
looks great. Eat it.  Come on, eat and drink some water.
I'm a [ __ ].
What's the noise here? Let me bring you some
water.
No, no, I won't. I'll come myself. I'll bring you some water. You
have to drink some water here. It wouldn't be
respectful to drink water in front of Mom and Dad.
I'll go inside and drink it.
Let it be a joke, what kind of hiccup
sound is that? Is it different? It makes a double-double sound.
[Laughter]
Look, even when you laugh,
you make a double-double sound.  This is called Echo.  If the Vastu is not
correct, it should be changed.
Can I rent this house?
Hey, this is a government quota, right?  Hey Velu, are
you still sleeping?  It's
eight o'clock, Entrida.
Look how he sleeps, curled up.  Velu came in and drank coffee.
Everything is thrown everywhere.   If
you ask me, I'll just sit around and
watch a movie or something like that, and just talk.
Mom, please read my mirror and
ask me everything.
Mom, what's up,
mom, come here and see, will you drink strong coffee and go
back to sleep?
Oh my
[screaming]
What's up, Raja?
Maruthamali Maruthamali Maruthamali Muruga, what's up, Muruga, Maruthamali, my dear, Muruga, is it your
duty to protect the family of the gods? What's up, what's up, what's up, what's up, what's up,
you don't have
Thaipusam today, you do
n't have Thaipusam today,
that's why I said I don't have Thaipusam,
can you forget Muruga for that?  Never, jattu
kudu sandalwood, jattu kudu sandalwood, gin chakka gin chakka gin jakka gin jakka,
mom, where did you get my pink dress? It's in
his pocket.
Why should I
take my dress?  My mother said that there are no dresses here, the
pink blouse is in the bathroom.
You don't have any dresses, you just want
to wear a pink blouse. Come on,
okay?
[Screaming] There's nothing
here. You're going to be too busy.
[Music]
Velu,
what are you doing? There's nothing there. You have to do
two things in the morning without fail
.
It's good for us to bow down to the Lord
.  I need to take a bath.  It's
good for all of us who are in need.
Go take a shower, have
you learned to speak properly?
Hey, you look like a pretty girl, you
look like a doll, you look like a girl
sitting inside.
Yes, I'm the one who brought a girl and
hid her under a doll.  Go and
see the work.
It's beautiful.  But there's something missing
.
[Screaming] Whatever you want
to put in there, I'll
put it in there myself.
Now you look beautiful, go take a
bath.